Erol Bicer, Ph.D.Nuclear Engineer



- erolbicer@live.com
- +82-10-7497-0705
- www.erolbicer.com
- in LinkedIn/erolbicer
- R⁶ ResearchGate/Erol-Bicer
- GitHub/nucerl
- South Korea

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Turkish - Fluent

Korean - Conversational

SYSTEM CODES

RELAP5 | MARS-KS | SPACE

CONTAINMENT CODES

GOTHIC | CAP

SEVERE ACCIDENT

MELCOR

CFD CODES

OpenFOAM | CUPID

CODING LANGUAGES

PYTHON | MATLAB | FORTRAN | C++ | HTML/CSS

TOOLS

ERP | Microsoft Project | Trello |
Jira | Git | PCTRAN | SNAP |
Origin | Salome | DOS/UNIX |
ParaView | CATIA | Mathcad

PROFILE

I have nine years of experience specializing in conducting comprehensive safety analyses for various nuclear power plants, using advanced system and computational fluid dynamics codes. My experience encompasses successfully developing, leading, and completing international projects through effective collaboration with diverse multinational and multicultural teams.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FNC Technology Co., Ltd. 🛮

Manager

2023 - present | South Korea

Associate Manager

2019 - 2023 | South Korea

Assistant Manager

2016 - 2019 | South Korea

Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd., R&D Engineer

2013 − 2014 | Ankara, Türkiye

EDUCATION

Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D., Seoul National University

2024 | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS ☑ 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

LATEST PROJECTS

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses Project Development and Management (APM)

[MSR] Development and Analysis of Fuel Salt Leakage Behavior in Discharge System Shell

Project Development and Management (APM)

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Analysis

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

CERTIFICATES AND AWARDS

Professional Engineer, KENCA

International Marketing, Business and Intelligence, ATO Modeling and Computation of Multiphase Flows, ETH International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

PERSONAL VENTURES

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder ☑